brightnow.com 2014-05-19

# Privacy Policy | Bright Now! Dental

## Smile Brands Privacy Policy

We at Smile Brands Inc. ("Smile Brands") are dedicated to protecting your privacy online when visiting our websites and, subject to this Online Privacy Policy (the "Policy"), we pledge to keep the information you share with us online confidential and secure.

Currently this Policy applies to all users of SmileBrands.com, brightnow.com, monarchdental.com, castledental.com and newportdental.com with respect to their use of these websites (the “Websites”). This Policy outlines the information Smile Brands will collect on the Websites and how we will use that information. By visiting one of the Websites, you are accepting the practices described in this Policy.

WE ARE RAPIDLY DEVELOPING OUR SERVICE TO MEET YOUR NEEDS AND, THEREFORE, SMILE BRANDS RESERVES THE RIGHT TO MODIFY THIS POLICY WITHOUT ADVANCE NOTICE. WE ASK THAT YOU PERIODICALLY CHECK THE POLICY FOR CHANGES AND TO INSURE FAMILIARITY WITH THE MOST CURRENT VERSION OF THE POLICY. HOWEVER, THIS PRIVACY POLICY IS NOT INTENDED TO, AND DOES NOT, CREATE ANY CONTRACTUAL OR OTHER LEGAL RIGHTS IN OR ON BEHALF OF ANY PARTY. 

## Our Privacy Pledge

Our privacy pledge to you is this: subject to the exceptions below, we will not share any private information that personally identifies you ("personal information") with any third party, unless we have your consent.

The only exceptions to this pledge are that we reserve the right to disclose personal information to protect our rights or property, to enforce our Terms and Conditions of Use, and to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate (including as required by operation of law or at the request of government regulators or other law enforcement officials or the courts)(these exceptions referred to herein collectively as the “Privacy Exceptions”). We shall have no duty to notify you of disclosures for these reasons.   

## What information do we collect, and how can you access it?

Smile Brands learns certain information about you from your visits to the Websites and what we do with this information depends on what you do when you are visiting the Websites. This Policy explains the uses we currently make of this information. This Policy lets you know what choices, access and security you have with respect to information Smile Brands collects.

Unless you register and create a profile, send us an e-mail, or use chat rooms and forums or other products and services that are or will be available on the Websites, we collect and store only the following information about you: the domain from which you accessed the Internet, the date and time you access the Websites, and the pages you visit most frequently. This information is not linked to a user name unless you give us one. We use the information to measure the number of visitors to various portions of our service and to help us improve our service. Our site will use cookies if you have chosen the option on your browser. Cookies help us customize and improve the Websites for you. You do not have to accept cookies to use the Websites; however, if you disable cookies, the Websites will not remember your customizations and cannot help you find what you want on the Websites most easily. If you accept cookies, you can delete them later by going to the preferences, tools or options menus of your browser.

If you do register and create a profile, create a user name and password, send us an e-mail, or use the chat rooms and forums or other products and services that will be available on the Websites, we will collect and store the information you enter. Obviously, what we collect depends upon what you enter. You can edit your profile by clicking Account. You can delete your profile by simply deleting all the data fields, which will cause our server to delete the information from its online form. We reserve the right to keep all information in an off-line form, for archival purposes or as otherwise required by law. 

## How is this information used?

If you do not consent to permit us to share your personal information with third parties, we will use that information only to track your visits to our web site, which enables us to learn more about what you, specifically, and our customers, in general, are expecting from our service.

If you do consent to allow us to share your personal information with third parties, we will only use that information according to the consent you give. We may use aggregate data (information about our base of users in general, from which all personally-identifying information has been removed) for any purpose.

Note that certain links on our web pages will take you off the Websites to web pages operated by third parties. Smile Brands will have no control over the information you enter or the cookies your browser accepts while on third parties' sites. You should examine the terms of use and privacy policies of other web pages whenever you leave one of the Websites.   

## Security

When we use personal information gathered through the Websites we will do so pursuant to this Policy. When we share personal information with third parties other than with respect to the Privacy Exceptions, we will require the third parties to enter confidentiality obligations similar to this Policy or other appropriate confidentiality obligations.  Smile Brands currently uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) to encrypt and protect the transmission of users' information and communications over the Internet.

Note, however, that e-mail communications may not be secure or private. If you send us an e-mail, your e-mail, like most non-encrypted Internet e-mail communications, may be accessed and viewed without your knowledge or permission while in transit to us. If you consider the information you are communicating to be confidential, please do not use e-mail. As an alternative, you may contact us by telephone at the numbers provided for various locations on the Websites. If you choose to communicate confidential information to us via e-mail, by pressing the "send" button, you acknowledge that you are transmitting information to us which may be intercepted by third parties and are authorizing us to respond to you by e-mail.

Smile Brands will make reasonable efforts to use the latest security technologies to ensure that the information its users provide is secure. However, we would like to remind its users that technology is no substitute for common sense. For this reason, we strongly encourage users to keep their login names and passwords secret and to change their password when they think they have become compromised. Furthermore, we recommend that our users communicate over secure channels wherever possible, disable the automatic login features found in some browsers, and empty their browser caches regularly.

## Public Forums

The Websites’ users may be provided with chat rooms, forums, message boards and/or newsgroups.  Please remember that any information disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

## Terms and Conditions of Use

If you choose to visit the Websites, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to the Terms and Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the State of California.  Our business changes constantly.  This Policy and the Terms and Conditions of Use will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Policy in effect at the time of use. 

## Children

Smile Brands serves general users of the World Wide Web. We support and comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and other laws and we do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13, nor do we share such information with third parties. Children under the age of 13 are not permitted to register and create a profile at the Websites.  See the FTC’s site at <http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/privacyinitiatives/childrens.html> for more tips on protecting children’s privacy online. 

## Business Transfers

As Smile Brands continues to develop its business, Smile Brands, one or more of its affiliates, or substantially all of the assets of Smile Brands or one or more of its affiliates, may be acquired. In such a transaction, personal information likely would be one of the transferred business assets.

## For more information

If you would like any more information about Smile Brands or its Online Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at [BNDfeedback@brightnow.com](mailto:BNDfeedback@brightnow.com).
